It's Christmas Eve and we are going to go celebrate being young and being alive.
The Holiday is a comedy, romance film directed by Nancy Meyers.
Two women, one American and one British, swap homes at
Christmastime following bad breakups.
Each woman finds romance with a local man but realizes that the
imminent return home may end the relationship.
Amanda Woods, played by Cameron Diaz.
Iris Simpkins, played by Kate Winslet.
Graham Simpkins, played by Jude Law.
Miles Dumont, played by Jack Black.
Arthur Abbott, played by Eli Wallach.
Ethan, played by Edward Burns.
Last Holiday is a 2006 American romantic comedy-drama film directed by
Wayne Wang and written by Jeffrey Price and Peter S.
The film is loosely based on the 1950 British film of the same name by J.
The film stars Queen Latifah as Georgia Byrd, a humble department store assistant who is
told that she has a rare brain condition and only has a few weeks to live.
She promptly decides to spend her remaining funds on a
luxury holiday in Europe before she dies.
Price and Seaman wanted John Candy for the main role but, after Candy's
death, Latifah's agent suggested a new version starring her.
Produced by Robert Zemeckis' ImageMovers, the film was
released by Paramount Pictures on January 13, 2006.
The film underperformed at the box office, having grossed $43.3 million against a budget of $45 million and received
mixed reviews from critics, though Latifah's performance was universally praised for her charm and humor.
The film explores themes of london, england, holiday, movie
business, christmas party, country house.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.